There was a time when a cry for help was only heard as far as your voice could travel.
كان هناك وقت حيث كان نداء النجدة يُسمع فقط بقدر ما كان بإستطاعة الصوت السفر.
Now things are different.
الأحوال الآن مختلفة.
Now someone can be heard in a matter of seconds
الآن يمكن للإنسان أن يُسمع في غضون ثواني.
all the way across the world.
في مختلف أرجاء العالم.
The internet has become a voice for the voiceless
أصبحت الأنترنت صوتا لمن لا صوت له.
A way to shine awareness on hidden corruption
طريقة لتسليط الضوء على قضايا الفساد المخفية
and it's changing the world.
و هي الآن تغير العالم.
[crowd chanting] The whole world is watching!
[الجموع تهتف] كل العالم يتفرج !
Except that freedom isn't available to everyone.
إعلم أن الحرية ليست متاحة للجميع.
Over a quarter of the world's population lives with government-imposed censorship
أكثر من ربع سكان العالم يعيشون في ظل حكومات تقوم بفرض الرقابة على مواطنيها
and that number is growing.
و هذا العدد في تزايد.
Politically sensitive sites like Facebook,
المواقع ذي الطابع السياسي كفايسبوك،
YouTube, Twitter, and Google,
يوتيوب، تويتر، وجوجل،
the exact sites that are bringing light to corruption and injustice,
نفس المواقع التي تعالج قضايا الفساد و الظلم،
are blocked.
محظورة.
But you can help
لكن بإمكانك المساعدة
by using Lantern.
بإستعمال البرنامج Lantern.
Lantern is a safe and secure free software
Lantern برنامج مؤمن و مجاني
that gives people internet access in places where access is denied.
الذي يمكن للأفراد إستعمال شبكة الأنترنت حتى في أماكن يكون فيه الدخول للشبكة محظورا.
It's software that circumvents government censorship.
إنه برنامج يقي من الرقابة الحكومية.
When you install Lantern on your computer
عند تثبيت البرنامج Lantern على جهازك
you provide a new escape route
تقوم بشق طريق آخر
for getting new information in and out of censored countries.
لإستقبال و إرسال المعلومات من و إلى البلدان المراقَبة.
You are giving people a way out
أنت تمد للأفراد طريفا للنجدة
a way to communicate
طريقا للإنصال
All of us are connected
كلنا متصلون
now more than ever.
الآن وأكثر من أي وقت مضى.
With a few simple steps, you have the power
بإتباع مراحل قليلة ويسيرة، فإن لك القدرة
to provide equal access to the internet
لإعطاء حق مماثل لإستعمال الأنترنت للكل
and help change the world.
والمساعدة على تغيير العالم.
Will you?
هل ستقوم بهذا ؟
Join the movement.
إنضم إلى الحركة
Join Lantern.
إنضم إلى البرنامج لانتيرن